financeworlds.com 2016-10-23

# Privacy Policy

What Does this Website Collect?

We use information you provide us on this website to link you with insurance companies which will offer you products or services. We do not ever give or sell your personal information to any outside company or website, beyond giving insurance companies the information necessary to generate a quote for you.

In the course of collecting information for your insurance quotes, we may ask your name, age, address, and phone number. This information is confidential and will not be given by us to any outside group or individual.

How Do You Use My Information?

The only reason we collect any personal information from you is to forward it to insurance companies who may be interested in giving you a rate quote. We do not compile or keep this information for any other purpose.

You may, if you choose, visit our website anonymously, but we cannot facilitate your free rate quotes without certain amounts of personal information. However, you are free to browse our site and read our blogs and informative articles without giving any personal information whatsoever.

Why Do You Need My Email?

If you are interested in receiving information from various sources on ways to save on car insurance, you can sign up for our free email service. We will periodically send you information, news, and other items related to car insurance. However, this is an option service; you are not required to sign up for it in order to use our website.

Do You Allow Third-Party Websites on this Site?

Yes, we occasionally allow third-party sites to advertise on our website. While we make every attempt to screen these third-party sites, we accept no responsibility for, nor do we have any control over, their content. If you click on a link for a third party website from this site, you will be redirected to another site and their privacy policy will apply to your browsing on that site.

Do You Collect IP Information?

We may, at our discretion, log IP addresses and other non-personal information for use in compiling statistics about visitors to our site. This information is not linked in any way with your name, nor will we ever sell or give this information to any third party.

By using our site, you consent to our privacy policy terms. If you have any questions, please contact us at the address on the Contact Us page.
